often times you want your function to
很多时候，当您不希望出现某些错误时，您希望功能失败
fail when something is not right in
solidity dirty wasted donor which was
坚实肮脏的浪费捐助者，这被停止了进一步执行
stopped the further execution of the
function being called the day wasted on
所谓的浪费天的功能是断言的需求，而韦伯在此
air are assert require and Weber in this
video we're gonna go over how to use
视频，我们将介绍如何使用它们，看看它们如何
each of them and see how they are
different from the other ones when a
与其他函数不同的是，当一个函数抛出错误时，它将撤消
function throws an error it will undo
all of the changes that were made in the
当前调用中所做的所有更改都类似于编程
current call similar to a programming
language like Python and JavaScript
Python和JavaScript错误之类的语言冒出来，这意味着如果您
errors bubble up this means that if you
call a function that calls another
调用一个函数，该函数调用另一个失败的函数，然后
function which fails with an air then
the function you called also fails with
在我向您展示示例之前，您调用的函数也同样失败了
the same air before I show you examples
of assert require and we burn first
肯定的需求，我们先烧，我们要写一个简单的合同，
we're gonna write a simple contract that
stores the balance of an account to
存储帐户余额以存储余额，我们将需要
store the balance we're gonna need a
public state variable and we're also
公共状态变量，我们还需要一个函数来存入
gonna need a function to deposit into
this contract and a function to withdraw
该合约和撤回该合约的功能存款功能将采取
from it the deposit function will take
in the amount to deposit and increment
存入金额，并以提款金额增加余额
the balance by the amount the withdrawal
function will taking the amount that you
函数将提取您要提取的金额并从中减去
want to withdraw and subtract it from
the balance now that we have a simple
现在我们有了一个可以模拟银行帐户的简单合约来平衡余额
contract that simulates a bank account
let's add validations using a sir
让我们使用需要先生和重生先生来添加验证
require and rebirth a sir is used to
check for conditions that should never
如果您的代码是
be possible if your code which is a
failing assertion then there's a serious
断言失败，那么您的代码中就有一个严重的错误需要修复，因此
bug in your code that you need to fix so
correct codes who never taught an error
正确的代码，在我们存入资金时从不从断言中教过错误
from an assertion when we make a deposit
we want to make sure that the balance
我们要确保更新余额后余额会增加
went up after updating the balance will
assert that the client balance is
断言客户余额大于或等于旧余额
greater than or equal to the old balance
this expression should always evaluate
如果不是，则此表达式应始终求值为true。
to true if it does not then this
assertion will turn and our transaction
断言将转而我们的交易将失败，并且当我们提款时我们想要
will fail and when we withdraw we want
to make sure that the balance went down
确保余额减少，所以我们断言余额增加了
so we assert that up
balance is destined or equal to the
余额注定或等于这两个断言的全部余额
whole balance these two assertions
should always evaluate to true however
应该始终评估为true，但是我们可以使这些断言失败，让我们
we can make these assertions fail let's
see how first we're gonna need a very
看看我们如何首先需要非常大的数量，所以让我们存储最大的数量
large number so let's store the largest
number possible for the datatype eland
合约内的数据类型eland可能的编号，然后进行编译，
inside their contract next compile and
deploy the contract deposit 1 and check
部署合同保证金1并检查我们的新余额，它应该是下一个
our new balance it should be one next
deposit this very large number and
存入非常大的数字，您会发现交易失败
you'll see that the transaction fails
click on the transaction log you can see
点击交易日志，您可以看到我们发送了三百万次喘息，而我们
that we sent three million gasps and we
used up all of it
所有这些都用完了，您可以在这里看到
furthermore you can see here that the
balance did not change since the
由于交易失败，余额没有变化，所以我只是向您显示
transaction failed so I just showed you
that when assertion fails it will use up
当断言失败时，它将耗尽您发送的所有来宾，并且
all of the guests that you send and
state changes will be undone so why did
状态更改将被撤消，所以为什么这个断言失败了，所以失败了，因为
this assertion fail it failed because
numbers and civility can overflow and on
数字和文明可能会溢出并在地板上，所以让我们来谈谈溢出
the floor so let's talk about overflow
and on the flow and then we'll come back
然后在流程上，然后我们将返回添加额外的验证，以便这些
to add extra validations so that these
two assertions will not fail imagine a
两个断言不会失败，假设一个时钟的时间范围是1到12，
clock that hours ranges from 1 to 12 and
any number greater than 12 will make
任何大于12的数字都会使时钟全天候旋转，最终
circles around the clock and eventually
band on a number between 1 and 12 for
1到12之间的数字上的带，例如13将围绕
example 13 will make a circle around the
clock once and stop at 1 and if you had
计时一次，然后从1停下来，如果您离时钟位置还有12个小时的话
12 hours from a position on the clock
you come back to the same exact position
您会回到相同的精确位置，例如，如果您有，则从7开始
so for example starting at 7 if you had
12 hours you come back to 7 in solidity
12个小时后，您将可靠地返回到7代表的数据类型
the data type youant which stands for
unsigned integer is similar to a clock
无符号整数类似于时钟，类似于范围为1的时钟
similar to a clock which ranges from 1
to 12 UN ranges from 0 to 2 to the 256
到12 UN的范围是从0到2到256减1，而不是从12开始
minus 1 and instead of starting at 12 it
starts at 0 like a clock any no
像时钟一样从0开始，不迟于2到256-一个将
later than two to the 256 - one will
wrap around and eventually fall in the
环绕并最终落在0到2到256减去1的范围内
range between 0 and 2 to the 256 minus 1
and like adding 12 hours to a time will
就像每次增加12个小时，您将回到原来的位置
get you back in the same position of the
clock adding 2 to the 256 - a number
时钟加2到256-一个数字会使您回到相同的数字，因此
will get you back to the same number so
let's say that X and y are 2 units there
假设X和y是2个单位，则x ly的总和可能是
is a possibility that the sum of x ly is
greater than 2 to the 256 minus 1 in
大于2等于256减1，在这种情况下，总和会环绕并
that case the sum wraps around and
starts counting from 0 this is called
从0开始计数，这被称为溢出，因此我们依次如何
overflow so let's in turn how we could
prevent our contract from overflowing
防止我们的合同首先溢出，我们知道将256加2
first we know that adding 2 to the 256
to X will give us back the same number
X将给我们第二个相同的数字，我们知道所有数字都更少
second we know that all numbers are less
than or equal to 2 to the 256 minus 1 so
等于或等于256减1的2，所以这意味着X加y会跌倒
this means that X plus y can over fall
but it can never reach back to X since Y
但它永远无法回到X，因为Y小于256的2，因此如果X
is less than 2 to the 256 therefore if X
plus y is greater than or equal to X and
加y大于或等于X，则没有溢出，如果X加
then there was no overflow and if X plus
y is less than X then we know that
y小于X，那么我们知道在流上发生的溢出是
overflow occurred on the flow is the
opposite of over for a number overflows
大于的相反数，当大于最大数时溢出
when it is greater than the maximum
range likewise a number under flows when
同样，范围在嵌套在最小范围内时在流量下的数字
it is nest in the minimum range in the
case of unsigned integers this happens
无符号整数的情况，当数字小于0时会发生这种情况，所以X
when the number is less than 0 so X
minus y will on the floor when Y is
当Y大于X时，减去y将在地板上，现在我们知道何时
greater than X now that we know when
numbers overflow and on the floor let's
数字溢出，在地板上，让我们回到我们的代码并添加其他内容
go back to our code and add extra
validations we know that X plus y does
验证我们知道，如果X加y大于X，则x加y不会溢出。
not overflow if X plus y is greater than
or equal to X replacing X with balance
或等于X用余额代替X并用L中的水代替X
and water from L we have balance plus
amount does not overflow if balance plus
如果余额加金额大于或等于金额，则金额不会溢出
amount is greater than or equal to
balance in other words there was no
换句话说，如果新的平衡很好，就不会有溢出
overflow if the new balance is great
then or equal to the old balance so
等于或等于旧余额，这就是我们需要的额外验证
that's the extra validation that we need
to make sure that our balance does not
确保我们的余额不会溢出，但是我们不应该使用先生
overflow but we shouldn't use a sir
since assertions should always evaluate
因为断言应该始终评估为true，所以这是我们使用require的地方
to true so this is where we use require
require is used to validate inputs state
require用于在执行之前验证输入状态条件并检查
conditions before execution and to check
outputs of other functions in this case
在这种情况下，我们将检查其他功能的输出
we're going to check that the New
Balance is greater than or equal to the
余额大于或等于旧余额，然后再更新余额
old balance before updating the balance
state variable when this condition is
当该条件不成立时的状态变量需要良好的供体，并且
not true require well donor and the
transaction will fail require accepts an
交易将失败，需要接受一个可选的错误消息，该消息将是
optional error message that will be
shown when it tells an error so you'll
当它告诉您错误时显示，以便您将消息溢出传递给
pass in the message overflow for the
error message if this condition passes
错误消息，如果此条件通过，则我们会将余额更新为新的
then we'll update the balance to our new
balance now this possession should
平衡，现在该拥有权应始终评估为真，因为
always evaluate to true since by the
time the call reaches a sign there was
当呼叫到达一个标志时，再也没有溢出，接下来让我们添加一些
no overflow next let's add some
validations to our withdrawal function
验证我们的提款功能，以便断言永远不会失败
so that the assertion never fails
we know that X minus y does not on the
我们知道，如果X大于或等于Y，则X减去y不会出现在流上
flow if X is greater than or equal to Y
replacing the variables the condition
替换变量，我们需要检查的条件是
that we need to check for is that the
balance is greater than or equal to the
余额大于或等于将要提取的金额
amount that were gonna withdraw
if the code reaches this mind and we
如果代码达到了这个目的，并且我们知道地板上没有任何东西，那么
know that there was no on the floor so
this assertion should always evaluate to
此断言应始终评估为true
true
that's deposit again and make sure that
再次存款，并确保我们的会话没有出错
our session does not do an error
compile and redeploy the contract
编制和重新部署合同
again deposit one and check that the
再次存入一笔，并检查余额是否正确
balance is correct
next deposit this very large number
下次再次存入这个非常大的数字，您可以在这里看到
again you can see here that the
transaction failed with the message
事务失败并显示消息溢出，这意味着存在一个
overflow this means that there was an
overflow and are required statement
溢出，并且要求语句失败，这也意味着该断言
failed it also means that the assertion
below they never executed when you check
下面它们在您检查事务日志时从未执行过，您可以看到
the transaction log you can see that not
all of the gas were used this shows that
所有的气体都被使用，这表明断言如果被执行则永远不会执行
the assertion was never executed if it
did it would have used up all of the gas
会不会像使用蜂鸣器一样消耗掉所有气体
the way you use beeper is similar to the
way you use require however Reber only
您使用的方式require但是Reber只接受一个参数错误消息
takes in one argument the error message
to be told so the way you will use River
被告知，所以您将使用River的方式是编写栓塞语句
is to write if statements for embolic
conditions when the invalid condition
当无效条件评估为真时的条件称为重生
evaluates to true we call the rebirth
function in this case the invalid
函数在这种情况下无效的条件是当余额为
condition is when the balance is
destined amount to be withdrawn when
当计算结果为true时要提取的预定金额，我们称为
that evaluates to true we call the
reverb function this revert statement
混响功能此revert语句的作用与
does exactly the same thing as the
require statement above River might be a
在条件较高的情况下，River语句可能是一个更好的选择
better choice to use when the condition
to check becomes more complex that
检查变得更加复杂，涵盖了如何使用断言的require和
covers how to use assert require and
rebirth
在这段视频中我们谈到了三个
in this video we talked about the three
ways to turn air assert require and
转变空中断言需求的方法，韦伯断言永远不应该评估为
Weber assertion should never evaluate to
false if it does then that means there's
如果为false，则表示代码中的错误未能通过断言
a bug in your code failing assertion
will use Apollo the gas that you sent
将使用阿波罗您随交易发送的气体由
with your transaction require is used by
all the inputs preconditions and other
所有输入前提条件和其他功能输出（如果需要）
function outputs when a require
statement fails it does not use up all
语句失败，在您使用以下语句的情况下，它不会耗尽所有气体
of the gas in situations where you use a
require you can also write an equivalent
要求您还可以使用Ebert编写等效的代码，但Weber更为实用
code using Ebert but Weber is more
useful than require when checking
比我在检查复杂条件时所需的功能要有用
complex conditions that's all I got for
this video thanks for watching and have
这部影片感谢您的收看，祝您度过愉快的一周
a nice week